# JON GREGORY

PHONE 303 909 1532 • E-MAIL | GREGORYSTRONG@GMAIL.COM

#### **SUMMARY**

Full stack developer, passionate about technology and continuous improvement is seeking a technical role which will assist in the corporate strategies to produce positive financial returns. Over the past 13 years I have become well versed in operations, engineering, and business development of the oil and gas industry. I am now taking the skill sets I have acquired over my career and integrating them with software engineering. I am confident that I would make a positive contribution and would appreciate your consideration of my skills in this application.

#### **PROJECTS**

Github Repository: <a href="https://github.com/jongregory75">https://github.com/jongregory75</a>

Portfolio: <a href="https://jongregory75.github.io/Portfolio/">https://jongregory75.github.io/Portfolio/</a>

https://github.com/jongregory75/MLB-Ballpark-Tracker

- React.js, MongoDB, Apollo Server, Apollo Client, bcrypt, Express.js, graphql, jsonwebtoken, mongoose, bootstrap, react-dom, react-router-dom, nodemon
- React.js based app to track ball park visits

# https://github.com/Ajurgs/Appointment-Scheduler

- Bcrypt, dotenv, Express.js, fullcalendar-scheduler, handlebars, mysql2, sequelize
- RESTful app to schedule service appointments

#### https://github.com/Chequelito/theDailyDive

• Multiple Web API app to deliver daily content to the user

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# 11/2007 - 8/2017 Halliburton Energy Services

# Engineer / Account Leader / Business Development Manager

- Responsible for understanding revenue/cost structures and pricing for all
  product service lines to multiple customers in the Rockies and western United
  States.
- Documented progressive leadership experience
- Continuous involvement in product development and associated stakeholders.
- Managed 30+ account reps covering multiple product / service lines.
- Responsible for roughly \$650,000,000.00 in yearly revenue.
- Guided engineering teams to produce value add, engineered solutions for common to complex problems.
- Presented performance reviews to customers.
- Built lasting relationships with customers from the C-suite to the engineering level.
- Responsible for creation of terms and conditions for customer contracts.
- Subject matter expert in oilfield cement engineering and operations.

# 6/2001 - 8/2007 Smart Solutions LLC.

- Consulted on a variety of solutions to 15+ clients.
- Skills: SQL, Java, JS, HTML, CSS

#### 11/2000 - 11/2001 Wellogix, Inc.

 Developed prototype applications for a startup petroleum exploration and drilling software company. Java, SQL, Oracle, JS, HTML, CSS

# 5/1999 - 11/2000 International Business Machines

- www.wiredscholar.com
- www.helzberg.com
- Sprint.com
- Skills: Java, SQL, Oracle, JS, HTML, CSS

### EDUCATION / TECHNICAL SKILLS

# 2021 - University of Denver - Full stack software

- HTML5
- JavaScript
- React.js
- MySql
- Bootstrap
- Heroku deployment
- Expres.js
- REST full applications

- CSS3
- JQuery
- Node.js
- MongoDB
- Responsive design
- Git/GitHub document management
- Authentication
- MVC application design

# 2012 - 2015 Texas A&M University - Mays Business School - Center for Executive Development

- Financial acumen
- Business Leadership Development I & II

# 1994 - 1999 Colorado State University

Ft. Collins, CO

• Bachelor Degree, Economics

#### AWARDS AND MEMBERSHIPS

# 2012 MVP - Halliburton Energy Services

- Award given by peers for top of class in Frontline Supervisor Training
- 2012 MVP Halliburton Energy Services.
- Award for providing engineered solutions to customers.

# 2000 Client Team Award - IBM

Award for outstanding engineered solutions